<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
				<rss version="2.0">
					<channel>
						<title>Pathway Communications RSS Feed</title>
						<link>http://www.pathcom.com</link>
				    	<item>
							 <title>Pathway is Hiring</title>
							 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=41</link>
							 <description><![CDATA[The Pathway Group of Companies is growing, and is accepting applications from talented and qualified individuals in the areas of application development, and sales. Contact us for further information.]]></description>
						 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Did You Know...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=2</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Established in 1995, Pathway Communications, was the first Canadian company to offer a unified portfolio of Internet, Network Integration and software development services from a single source. 

Our Managed Internet and Data Centre and co-location Services are available in Ontario, Quebec, British Columbia, Alberta, Manitoba and Nova Scotia.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Online Security</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=29</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Exercise caution when reading emails to protect your passwords and identity. Pathway Communications would never request sensitive information over email. If you have questions or concerns about an email or call you've received, <a href="http://pathcom.com/contactus/index.php">contact us</a> immediately.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Pathway moves to its new office building!</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=22</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[On October 19th, 2009, the Pathway Group moved to its own new, spacious, state-of-art office located in the heart of Markham, Canada's high-technology hub.

Our new facility houses offices as well as a custom-built, high-density, Tier III Data Centre, which has been rigorously engineered to meet the most stringent environmental, security and safety standards. <a href=http://www.pathcom.com/company/office_announcement.php Target='_blank' >Learn more...</a>]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>High Marks In Customer Satisfaction</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=21</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Every year Pathway conducts a Customer Satisfaction Survey to get feedback from our residential customers on various aspects of our service, including our technical knowledge, response times to queries, and more. This year we were gratified to learn that our scores <a href=http://www.pathcom.com/products/winners.php target=_blank>had increased</a> over last year in a number of key areas.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Development Opportunities</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=37</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Do you find yourself intrigued by the world of open source?
Do you want to increase your knowledge of modern programming technologies?
Pathway Communications has begun to accept registrations for developers looking to work with us for the purposes of improving our products.  Click <a href=http://developer.pathcom.com>here</a> for more information and to sign up.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>These Days...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=6</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Harsh economic realities raise questions about spending and efficiency. Infrastructure and operating costs are under your magnifying glass.

Call to find out more about how Pathway can help you shore up your IT infrastructure and operations.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Did You Know...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=8</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Pathway offers 24/7 technical support. Your inquiries, concerns and comments are always appreciated. Real-time systems allow us to detect, track, and solve incidents, and all within our written commitments to you -- our SLAs. 

It comes as no surprise that Pathway has maintained ISO certification for its quality standards for over 12 years.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Certified...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=1</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Pathway Communications has the distinction of being showcased as a success story by Sun Microsystems and was the first Internet Service Provider in the world to acquire ISO 9002 certification.

Pathway is now certified under the new ISO 9001-2008 standard and all key technical staff and managers are ITIL certified.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Your Choice...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=4</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[In 2008, Pathway was proud to receive the Consumers' Choice Award for Business Excellence as an outstanding Internet Service Provider and for Customer Satisfaction in Toronto, Ontario.

Pathway strives to help businesses grow by providing the assurance of quality and exceptional customer service.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Did You Know...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=7</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[The Pathway group of companies (Pathway, Netpulse, Teliuvo and Citenet) offer a suite of products and services spanning connectivity, managed services and hosting, as well as information technology and business process outsourcing (ITO and BPO), with points of presence across major Canadian cities.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Did you know...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=9</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Pathway was the first company to launch bonded ADSL  and MPLS in Western Canada. ]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Gift Of Gab...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=10</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.smartreach.ca">SmartReach</a>, our mobile long distance product offers the best rates on calls around the world, whether it's to a landline or a cell phone. And since we own all our telephony equipment and network infrastructure, we can directly maintain exceptional voice quality.]]></description>
							 </item>
					    	<item>
								 <title>Big Bandwidth...</title>
								 <link>http://www.pathcom.com/company/news_articles.php?id=5</link>
								 <description><![CDATA[Pathway offers the fastest bonded ADSL service in Western Canada, with uploading speeds of 3.2 Mbps, and downloading speeds of 10 Mbps. That means increased productivity, meeting your deadlines, or just not having to wait for hours while you upload your work to the head office.]]></description>
							 </item></channel>
						 </rss>